Guide to the Charles and Shirley Weiss Collection of Opera Ephemera, 1951-2003 RL.11139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- The Crucible (Duke University, Durham, NC), 1986 January 9 (Box 1)
- The Crucible (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1989 July 1 (Box 1)
- The Crucible (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 January 25 (Box 1)
- Cue 67 (Virginia Opera, Norfolk, VA), 1996 January 24 (Box 1)
- The Cunning Little Vixen (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 April 18 (Box 1)
- The Cunning Little Vixen (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1993 March 14 (Box 1)
- The Cunning Little Vixen (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 November 5 (Box 1)
- Curlew River (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1997 June 1 (Box 1)
- The Dangerous Liaisons (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 September 21 (Box 1)
- The Dangerous Liaisons (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 March 18 (Box 1)
- Daphne (Duke University, Durham, NC?), 1996 July 20 (Box 1)
- Daphne (Duke University, Durham, NC?), 1996 August 7 (Box 1)
- Daphne (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 June 30 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 26 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1982 August 1 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 June 2 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1986 August 10 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 October 22 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 October 15 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 May 1 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 February 1 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 March 22 (Box 1)
- Das Rheinbold (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 2001 August 21 (Box 1)
- Das Verratene Meer (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1991 November 23 (Box 1)
- Dead Man Walking (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 October 19 (Box 1)
- Dead Man Walking (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 September 26 (Box 1)
- A Death in the Family (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1986 June 19 (Box 1)
- Death in Venice (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 February 26 (Box 1)
- Death in Venice (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 September 17 (Box 1)
- The Death of Klinghoffer (Brooklyn Academy of Music, Brooklyn, NY), 1991 September 13 (Box 1)
- The Death of Klinghoffer (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 November 7 (Box 1)
- Desert of Roses (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1992 February 22 (Box 1)
- The Desperate Husband (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1979 May 25 (Box 1)
- The Devil and Kate (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1990 June 21 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 January 5 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1982 November 14 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 March 21 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1990 February 10 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (Arizona State Univ. Lyric Opera Theatre, Tempe, AZ), 1993 December 1 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 February 25 (Box 1)
- Dialogues of the Carmelites (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1999 July 31 (Box 1)
- Dido and Aeneas (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2001 June 4 (Box 1)
- La Dirindina (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1999 June 13 (Box 1)
- Le Docteur Miracle (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1980 May 25 (Box 1)
- Le Docteur Miracle (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1980 May 28 (Box 1)
- Doktor Faust (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 January 29 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 March 3 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 7 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1986 September 13 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (Opera Colorado, Denver, CO), 1991 May 3 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 November 19 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 November 4 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 October 14 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 October 27 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2001 March 19 (Box 1)
- Don Carlo (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2001 April 29 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Reynolds Coliseum, Raleigh, NC), 1975 November 4 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 March 25 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1981 June 24 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1984 November 21 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Page Auditorium, Durham, NC), 1989 March 23 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 October 19 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1991 November 20 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1992 July 4 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1993 June 19 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 October 14 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 November 18 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 December 11 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1996 July 5 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 March 16 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1999 October 31 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Memorial Hall, Chapel Hill, NC), 1999 November 2 (Box 1)
- Don Giovanni (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 October 6 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Carolina Theatre, Durham, NC), 1978 June 25 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 January 6 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 29 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1983 August 10 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Jones Auditorium, Meredith College, Raleigh, NC), 1990 February 28 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1993 January 26 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 November 7 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1996 August 24 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1996 September 27 (Box 1)
- Don Pasquale (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1998 June 17 (Box 1)
- Don Quichotte (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1981 December 12 (Box 1)
- Don Quichotte (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 October 5 (Box 1)
- Don Quichotte (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 November 14 (Box 1)
- Dona Francisquita (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 February 7 (Box 1)
- The Dream of Valentino (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1994 January 17 (Box 1)
- A Dream Play (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1998 August 1 (Box 1)
- A Dream Play (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1998 August 14 (Box 1)
- The Dreyfus Affair (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1996 April 11 (Box 1)
- Il Duca d'Alba (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1992 May 22 (Box 1)
- A Dylan Thomas Triology (National Symphony Orchestra, Washington, DC), 1999 March 13 (Box 1)
- El Gato Montes (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 February 2 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Bayerische Staatsoper Nationaltheater Munchen, Munich, Germany), 1977 July 17 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 February 1 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 5 (Box 1)
- Elektra (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1990 March 12 (Box 1)
- Elektra (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1991 November 26 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Opera de Paris Bastille, Paris, France), 1992 March 20 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1992 May 29 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1992 October 12 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 January 15 (Box 1)
- Elektra (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 March 19 (Box 1)
- Elektra (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 October 18 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 2000 January 16 (Box 1)
- Elektra (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2000 July 26 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Kansallisooppera, Helsinki, Finland), 1966 August 31 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Durham Arts Council Street Opera, Durham, NC), 1989 June 9 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Opera Colorado, Denver, CO), 1991 May 4 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 November 9 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 November 21 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 January 28 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 December 7 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 February 6 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2000 February 4 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 March 2 (Box 1)
- L'Elisir d'Amore (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 November 8 (Box 1)
- Emmeline (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1996 July 27 (Box 1)
- Emmeline (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1996 August 9 (Box 1)
- Emmeline (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1998 April 11 (Box 1)
- L'Enfant et les Sortileges (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 March 13 (Box 1)
- L'Enfant et les Sortileges (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 11 (Box 1)
- L'Enfant et les Sortileges (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1999 March 25 (Box 1)
- L'Enfant et les Sortileges (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1999 March 25 (Box 1)
- L'Enfant et les Sortileges (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 March 16 (Box 1)
- Les Enfants Terribles (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1996 June 4 (Box 1)
- The English Cat (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1985 August 6 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 November 10 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 March 26 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (The Dallas Opera, Dallas, TX), 1986 April 25 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1986 June 21 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1994 July 16 (Box 1)
- Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 January 24 (Box 1)
- Ermione (Opera Omaha, Omaha, NB), 1992 September 19 (Box 1)
- Ermione (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2000 July 19 (Box 1)
- Ernani (Teatro Dell'Opera Roma, Rome, Italy), 1961 December 20 (Box 1)
- Ernani (Teatro alla Scala, Milan, Italy), 1982 December 28 (Box 1)
- Ernani (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 November 18 (Box 1)
- Ernani (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 March 9 (Box 1)
- Ernani (Opera Orchestra of New York, New York, NY), 1997 April 6 (Box 1)
- Erwartung (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 7 (Box 1)
- Erwartung (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 February 4 (Box 1)
- Esther (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 8 (Box 1)
- L'Etoile (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 November 7 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 April 14 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 February 21 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 4 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 February 16 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1991 June 22 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (English National Opera, London, England), 1994 March 31 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 April 5 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 November 19 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 October 20 (Box 1)
- Eugene Onegin (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2002 July 6 (Box 1)
- L'Euridice (Teatro della Pergola, Florence, Italy), 1980 June 13 (Box 1)
- Europera 5 (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1996 May 29 (Box 1)
- The Excursions of Mr. Broucek (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1996 May 29 (Box 1)
- Falstaff (Glyndebourne Festival Opera, East Sussex, UK), 1977 July 11 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Glyndebourne Festival Opera, East Sussex, UK), 1980 June 9 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Theatre Nationale Opera de Paris, Paris, France), 1982 December 18 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 March 15 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1986 July 13 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1989 September 23 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 October 3 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1994 June 25 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 February 3 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1996 May 25 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Opera Company of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA), 1997 April 28 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 October 26 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2001 June 30 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 November 10 (Box 2)
- Falstaff (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 April 9 (Box 2)
- La Fanciulla Del West (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1985 May 24 (Box 2)
- La Fanciulla Del West (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1991 July 13 (Box 2)
- La Fanciulla Del West (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 February 26 (Box 2)
- La Fanciulla Del West (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1995 July 15 (Box 2)
- Faust (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1985 July 7 (Box 2)
- Faust (New York City Opera, Raleigh, NC), 1985 October 24 (Box 2)
- Faust (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1986 October 18 (Box 2)
- Faust (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1987 October 18 (Box 2)
- Faust (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 March 24 (Box 2)
- Faust (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 January 19 (Box 2)
- Faust (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1994 November 15 (Box 2)
- Faust (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 November 16 (Box 2)
- Faust (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 February 5 (Box 2)
- Faust (Opera Colorado, Denver, CO), 1997 May 11 (Box 2)
- Faust (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1998 June 20 (Box 2)
- La Favorita (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 February 25 (Box 2)
- La Favorite (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 October 5 (Box 2)
- Fedora (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1994 October 24 (Box 2)
- Fedora (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 October 12 (Box 2)
- Fedora (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1998 November 9 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 October 6 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 February 2 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 March 26 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 December 5 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1988 February 26 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 November 1 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1993 April 15 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 2 (Box 2)
- Fidelio (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1994 May 27 (Box 2)
- The Fiery Angel (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 October 19 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (The National Opera Company, Raleigh, NC), 1976 May 7 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 September 27 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1990 June 21 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 September 24 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1994 January 18 (Box 2)
- La Fille du Regiment (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1994 February 26 (Box 2)
- La Finta Giardiniera (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1988 June 10 (Box 2)
- La Finta Giardiniera (Glimmerglass Opera, Cooperstown, NY), 1996 August 24 (Box 2)
- La Finta Giardiniera (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 January 31 (Box 2)
- Flavio (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2003 April 23 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Operan Stockholm, Stockholm, Sweden), 1963 August 19 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1980 June 19 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 27 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (The National Opera Company, Durham, NC), 1982 April 6 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1982 August 9 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1983 December 25 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1984 June 28 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1986 August 5 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 December 20 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 January 16 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1989 July 2 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 January 13 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1990 March 2 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1992 July 11 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1998 October 13 (Box 2)
- Die Fledermaus (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 December 13 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 March 23 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1987 July 10 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 February 1 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 March 6 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Los Angeles Music Center Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1995 September 18 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 October 17 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1998 October 31 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2001 March 14 (Box 2)
- Der Fliegende Hollander (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2002 May 24 (Box 2)
- Florencia en el Amazonas (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1996 October 27 (Box 2)
- Florencia en el Amazonas (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1997 October 15 (Box 2)
- Florencia en el Amazonas (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2001 April 28 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 September 25 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 October 20 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1984 October 31 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1989 March 3 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 November 6 (Box 2)
- La Forza del Destino (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 February 29 (Box 2)
- Four Saints in Three Acts (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1996 February 9 (Box 2)
- Francesca da Rimini (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1984 March 9 (Box 2)
- Francesca da Rimini (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 March 13 (Box 2)
- Die Frau ohne Schatten (Bayerische Staatsoper Nationaltheater Munchen, Munich, Bavaria), 1977 July 19 (Box 2)
- Die Frau ohne Schatten (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 March 24 (Box 2)
- Die Frau ohne Schatten (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 October 29 (Box 2)
- Die Frau ohne Schatten (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 December 17 (Box 2)
- Der Freischutz (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 November 1 (Box 2)
- From the House of the Dead (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1990 September 14 (Box 2)
- From the Towers of the Moon (UNC-CH Opera Theater Workshop, Chapel Hill, NC), 2002 April 19 (Box 2)
- The Gambler (English National Opera, London, England), 1990 March 17 (Box 2)
- The Gambler (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 March 27 (Box 2)
- The Gardens of Adonis (Opera Omaha, Omaha, NB), 1992 September 18 (Box 2)
- The Ghosts of Versailles (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 April 12 (Box 2)
- The Ghosts of Versailles (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 November 6 (Box 2)
- Gianni Schicchi (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 October 30 (Box 2)
- Gianni Schicchi (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 September 30 (Box 2)
- Gianni Schicchi (Opera Memphis, Memphis, TN), 1997 January 25 (Box 2)
- Gianni Schicchi (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1999 May 28 (Box 2)
- Gianni Schicchi (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 September 25 (Box 2)
- Giasone (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1998 May 24 (Box 2)
- La Gioconda (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 December 7 (Box 2)
- La Gioconda (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 September 25 (Box 2)
- La Gioconda (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1983 November 24 (Box 2)
- La Gioconda (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 February 3 (Box 2)
- La Gioconda (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1998 October 19 (Box 2)
- Giulio Cesare (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1981 March 15 (Box 2)
- Giulio Cesare (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 April 14 (Box 2)
- Giulio Cesare (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 2000 January 15 (Box 2)
- Giulio Cesare (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 March 9 (Box 2)
- The Glass Blowers (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 April 16 (Box 2)
- Gotterdammerung (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1982 August 6 (Box 2)
- Gotterdammerung (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 June 8 (Box 2)
- Gotterdammerung (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1986 August 15 (Box 2)
- Gotterdammerung (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 May 6 (Box 2)
- Gotterdammerung (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 2001 August 26 (Box 2)
- Goya (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1985 November 15 (Box 2)
- La Grande-Duchesse de Gerolstein (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1979 August 6 (Box 2)
- La Grande-Duchesse de Gerolstein (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1982 April 24 (Box 2)
- La Grande-Duchesse de Gerolstein (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1983 November 25 (Box 2)
- La Grande-Duchesse de Gerolstein (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2001 June 23 (Box 2)
- The Great Gatsby (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 December 20 (Box 2)
- The Great Gatsby (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 October 23 (Box 2)
- Griffelkin (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 7 (Box 2)
- Il Guarany (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1996 November 18 (Box 2)
- Guillaume Tell (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 November 18 (Box 2)
- H.M.S. Pinafore (New York Gilbert Sullivan Players, Chapel Hill, NC), 2002 January 28 (Box 2)
- Hamlet (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2002 June 21 (Box 2)
- Hansel and Gretel (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 December 18 (Box 2)
- Hansel and Gretel (Volksoper, Vienna, Austria), 1982 December 23 (Box 2)
- Hansel and Gretel (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1997 October 29 (Box 2)
- Harrison Loved His Umbrella (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1981 May 26 (Box 2)
- Harvey Milk (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1995 April 13 (Box 2)
- Harvey Milk (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1996 November 21 (Box 2)
- Herodiade (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 November 25 (Box 2)
- L'Heure Espagnole (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1999 March 25 (Box 2)